(Howard:)Okay, talk soon.
(Bernadette:)What's so great?
(Howard:)It looks like I'm going into space
after all, heh.
(Bernadette:)Howie, that's wonderful.
(Howard:)Uh-huh, wonderful.
Yay!
(Bernadette:)What happened?
I thought they cancelled your mission.
They... They did.
But NASA really wants my telescope...
(Howard:)...up on the space station, so they're
putting me on an earlier launch.
(Bernadette:)When?
(Howard:)A week from Friday.
(Bernadette:)What? We're getting married
that Sunday.
You're right, heh. L... I can't go to space.
l have to get married...
(Howard:)...and no one can say that's not
a good reason. I'll call him back.
Wait. I don't wanna be the one
who stands in your way.
(Howard:)Well, too bad, you already did.
It's a done deal. But I forgive you.
No. That's not how I wanna start
our marriage.